本字幕由天满宫字幕组制作，翻译:neko，字幕:neko 校对:neko，cinewamage，请在下载后24小时内删除，若因私自传播造成的法律责任，字幕君概不负责。
I know you all are very busy.
我知道你们都很忙。
I just want to thank everyone for helping me over the years,
我只是想感谢大家这些年来对我的帮助。
and this time with Men on Edge.
这次是和《Men on Edge》一起。
Thank you very much.
非常感谢。
And to my fellow directors, too, for your support.
还有我的同行导演们，也感谢你们的支持。
Melanie's here, thank you.
梅兰妮在这里，谢谢。
And Tom Cat, always asking for your opinion.
汤姆猫总是问你们的意见。
I just love seeing Donna around.
我就是喜欢看到唐娜在附近。
She just intimidates the hell out of me, but I just love her.
她让我感到非常害怕，但我却爱她。
And when people say it's a dream come true,
当人们说这是一个梦想成真的时候，
Man on Edge, it's literally a dream come true for me because as a teenager I used
《边缘人》对我来说真的是梦想成真，因为在我十几岁的时候，
to dream this stuff up in my stepfather's barn back in Illinois. I'm not
我曾在伊利诺伊州继父的谷仓里幻想过这些事情。我不会
telling you what I was doing at a time, okay? So yesterday I just had a model, you
告诉你那时候我在做什么，好吗？昨天我刚刚和一个模特合作，
know, telling me that this is like the best thing that he has ever done.
他告诉我这是他做过的最棒的事情。
Yesterday, Josh, my witness, and he said, whoa, it's porn but it's like art.
昨天，我的见证人Josh说，哇，这是色情但却像艺术。
I go, wow, that's great, right? Why not have, you know,
我去，哇，那太棒了，对吧？
your porn with a little bit of art so that was amazing and I'm hoping that man
为什么不把你的色情片和一点艺术结合起来，那太棒了，
on edge is the it's the little sight that could so thank you everyone thank you.
我希望边缘人就是那个小小的视角，所以谢谢大家，谢谢。
Cheese,Thank you.
干杯，谢谢你们
I'm playing the side trailer so some people haven't seen it yet
我正在播放侧边的预告片，所以有些人还没有看到。
here we go
我们开始吧